// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "We went___at the wekend?",
    answer: "shoping",
    options: [
      "the shops",
      "shoping",
      "to shops",
      "shops"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What____to night?",
    answer: "are they doing",
    options: [
      "they do",
      "do they do",
      "are they doing",
      "are they do"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "We go shoping____mont?",
    answer: "twice",
    options: [
      "every a",
      "every to",
      "twice",
      "once"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "My birthday is on February____?",
    answer: "10th",
    options: [
      "10rd",
      "10st",
      "10th",
      "10nd"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What____your father look like",
    answer: "does",
    options: [
      "Is",
      "are",
      "do",
      "does"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 6,
    question: "____You like a coffee?",
    answer: "would",
    options: [
      "will",
      "did",
      "would",
      "do"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "We___born 1985",
    answer: "were",
    options: [
      "is",
      "was",
      "were",
      "did"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "____She like sport?",
    answer: "does",
    options: [
      "do",
      "is",
      "does",
      "dont"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Do you like____DVDs",
    answer: "watching",
    options: [
      "watch",
      "watching",
      "to watching",
      "watches"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "I____a student of English",
    answer: "am",
    options: [
      "am",
      "are",
      "aren't",
      "is"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 11,
    question: "When___have lunch",
    answer: "does he",
    options: [
      "is he",
      "do he",
      "hes",
      "does he"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 12,
    question: "They___their homework",
    answer: "are doing",
    options: [
      "are do",
      "are doing",
      "did",
      "does"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 13,
    question: "The cinema is___the bank",
    answer: "opposite",
    options: [
      "next",
      "in front",
      "under",
      "opposite"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 14,
    question: "They____fly to India",
    answer: "didn't",
    options: [
      "didn't",
      "haven't",
      "doesn't",
      "has"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 15,
    question: "____you spoken to Janny",
    answer: "did",
    options: [
      "did",
      "have",
      "do",
      "has"
    ]
   }
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];